<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cryptos on Agr0 Hacks Stuff</title>
    <link>https://agrohacksstuff.io/crypto/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cryptos on Agr0 Hacks Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 05:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://agrohacksstuff.io/crypto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cracking Easy Crypto</title>
      <link>https://agrohacksstuff.io/crypto/easycrypto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 05:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrohacksstuff.io/crypto/easycrypto/</guid>
      <description>On any given CTF where crypto is involved, I almost always see basically the same challenge every time. You are given a background on how you&amp;rsquo;ve intercepted the encryption oracle, but not the decryption oracle, along with some ciphertext that you are instructed to decrypt somehow. Usually it goes something like this (and I&amp;rsquo;m drawing some parallels to a CTF challenge that is currently running right now, so I&amp;rsquo;m intentionally being vague):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bit Flipping</title>
      <link>https://agrohacksstuff.io/crypto/bitflipping/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 05:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrohacksstuff.io/crypto/bitflipping/</guid>
      <description>Bit flipping is another one of those magical attack techniques that a lot of people seem to want to write off as &amp;ldquo;I think there&amp;rsquo;s a tool that does that automatically for you.&amp;rdquo; And yeah I&amp;rsquo;m sure there&amp;rsquo;s a bunch. The concept itself seems relatively straight forward. I mean, for the most part a bit can only be in one of two states, so just change a 1 to a 0 or vice versa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PyNigma, and How I Made It</title>
      <link>https://agrohacksstuff.io/crypto/pynigma/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrohacksstuff.io/crypto/pynigma/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve said this before through various iterations, but some people work on cars, some build models, I write code to imitate an old cipher device from World War II. While I&amp;rsquo;ve named this code &amp;ldquo;PyNigma,&amp;rdquo; it is perhaps a bit more like Typex considering the amount of rotors used in this process. When I designed this, I didn&amp;rsquo;t have any sort of intention on inventing something new, this was definitely a hobbyist project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mersenne Twister Predictor In Action</title>
      <link>https://agrohacksstuff.io/crypto/mt-in-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 11:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrohacksstuff.io/crypto/mt-in-action/</guid>
      <description>In a previous post, I explained the very broad mechanism of what to do to predict the Mersenne Twister pseudo-random number generator. I only posted the functions but never actually showed them in action. That said, I have spun up some proof-of-concept code to explain how it can be used in practice. Given 624 samples of extracted pseudo-random numbers from one seed, I can re-create the state array and predict every single number generated from this extraction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pseudo Random Number Generators (and why you should tread lightly)</title>
      <link>https://agrohacksstuff.io/crypto/mt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 11:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrohacksstuff.io/crypto/mt/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always had some sort of weird nerdy interest in pseudo-random number generators. How is it that a computer, an object based solely on a deterministic approach to everything, can generate a number that is supposedly random? Well TL;DR, it simply can&amp;rsquo;t. Well, not without relying on external factors that are unreasonable to predict. One such example is Linux using things like timing of keystrokes and mouse movements, and other such readings from hard-to-predict motions of the internal mechanisms of the hard drive to generate enough entropy to generate a seed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
